<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shaastra Samvad</string>
    <string name="about_us">Shaastra Samvad, which means "Discussion on the Scriptures," aims to uncover information that has been buried under thousands of years of history and remains unexplored. This platform focuses on sharing information, fostering discussions, and promoting understanding for a better future. It is dedicated to preserving and sharing lesser-known facts and information from ancient Indian scriptures, such as Dhanurveda, Mahabharata, and Ramayana, in a way that is accessible to people of all ages. The current content on the app is centered around the weapons and fighting techniques described in Dhanurveda - Vasishta. The objective of the website is to educate and enlighten users about ancient Indian knowledge that has been long forgotten or overlooked.</string>
    <string name="mission">The purpose of this app is to illuminate the darkness with knowledge, to replace ignorance with wisdom, and to uphold righteousness over wrong. It will be a repository of ancient Indian scriptures, providing resources for people worldwide to explore and learn from these timeless texts. By fostering an understanding and appreciation of our heritage, it aims to inspire future generations to build a better future based on the wisdom of the past.</string>
    <string name="vision">"Shaastra-samvad is an endless project aimed at reviving and sharing the wisdom of ancient Indian scriptures. The app's scope is expanding beyond Dhanurveda to include texts like Mahabharata, Ramayana, and others. It will continue to grow and serve as a valuable resource for those interested in ancient Indian knowledge. The platform is dedicated to maintaining the authenticity and integrity of the information, ensuring that future generations can access and learn from these timeless scriptures."</string>
    <string name="gunmushti">Different Draw Techniques in Indian Archery - FAQ is video which shows practical use of The 5 different draw techniques of gunmushti, provides more information about gunmushti techniques, uploaded by youtube channel Armin Hirmer. All the techniques are performed by archer Armin Hirmer. All rights of this video are reserved by channel Armin Hirmer. You can click image below and check it out.</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Feel free to reach out to us for sponsorship, advertising, partnerships, collaboration, donations/support via the email provided.</string>
    <string name="email">shaastrasamvad@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="feedback">Give us your valuable feedback for the app. You can mention improvements, suggestions, and your thoughts for further enhancing the app and its content.</string>
    <string name="donate">Your generous contribution will help us make a difference!</string>
</resources>